{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find out from amongst the four alternatives as to how the pattern would appear when the transparent sheet is folded at the dotted line.\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 (X) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (1) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (2) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (3) \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 (4)", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}